[ED.
Loken.
This is Shearin.
I'm Milten.
We are the team
I'm Jearin.
Today is the day after the tour and Hiroshima Park!
Yay!
So, where are we?
Where is this place?
Miyajima!
Yay!
What a surprise! The world's largest Japanese-made island!
Miyajima!
Yay!
No, it's my first time. I'm coming to Kichijima!
It's my first time on a new island.
So I'm really looking forward to it.
Kii recommended some food.
You two look so cute looking at each other.
I want to make lots of fun memories together!
That's all for now.
Let's have fun today.
What do you think?
What do you recommend today, Kii?
It's been 8 years since I've been to Miyajima.
I haven't been to Miyajima in about 8 years.
I haven't been here for a long time.
I feel as if it's my first time here.
I want to find lots of delicious food.
I want to have fun.
What shall we eat?
I have a curiosity.
I want to try the deep-fried mamiji buns.
Then let's try the fried mamiji kara.
I want a fried mamiji.
I wonder where it is.
Aged mamiji
What a deep-fried maple manju!
I found it!
You found it!
Petrocci's Lemon
Rare cheese, cream, kosher
It's so hard to decide!
But Kosian is good, too, isn't it?
Cream or Koschian?
Which one?
I don't know.
What about you, Momochan?
Rare cheese.
I'll go with the cream.
Cream.
No.
So I got the fried maple!
Yay!
Well then...
What are you doing, Sukie?
Kosian.
Wow!
Rare cheese for you and cream for me!
Wow, it looks delicious! Let's have some of that.
So sweet!
The fried part is so crispy!
It's so different from the regular uncooked Gomijiman.
Amazing!
You just ate fried Gomijiman, didn't you?
Yes, thank you!
What are we going to eat now?
Ah?
Ana?
Anako?
I'm going to eat anko.
I'm off!
Yay!
So I'm going to eat Mr. Fujitani's anako rice now!
I'm serious.
I can make it fly in the palm of my hand.
Let's go!
Wow!
I'm so excited about this!
Se-oh!
This is bad for me
I've never had anko (sea cucumber)
Right?
You've never been to anko shop before, right?
That's great!
Music
Aaah! Amazing!
Congratulations!
Awesome!
Yum! Looks so good!
Good eating size!
Music
Looks so good!
♪ Music
Mmm!
Wow! Wow!
Wow!
Wow!Wow!
Ah!
My mom made this for me.
I knew it!
I'll eat it right now.
Bon appétit!
I love sweet toppings.
Please make it.
Really.
You can smell your mother's scent in front of you.
Delicious.
It's really delicious.
It smells so rich.
It's sweet and delicious.
I'll try it with everyone.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for the food.
Delicious!
Happiness is spilling out!
Here we are at the Miyagi Bay Aquarium!
Look, a cute little white doe!
We were not allowed to take pictures inside the aquarium.
So I'll leave you with some pictures of us and the lovely fish!
Let's go!
Shooting the fish's buttocks
Take a picture of a fish's butt
Shooting buttocks
Shoot the butt
Shoot buttocks
Shoot the ass
Shooting buttocks
Yes, so I've seen the aquarium.
It was fun!
And Momo won the quiz at Neusteel's.
He bought her a souvenir as a reward!
May I?
Wow, that's a lot of stuff!
I thought we'd all remember this.
What a win!
They bought it for me!
I'm so happy.
Here you go.
And look at the color!
Look at this, ladies and gentlemen.
Three of our favorite paintings!
I'll treasure them.
Me too.
So that's the end of the Siminta View of Miyajima.
I'm so glad we were able to make such great memories!
It was really fun!
So goodbye everyone!
Bye bye!
Have a great and happy day when you get to see it!